selectarticle.net 2018-03-20

# Privacy Policy

DMCA

It is our policy to respond to notices of alleged infringement that comply with the United States Digital Millennium Copyright Act ("DMCA") or other applicable law.

If you have a good faith belief that a copyright in your work has been infringed on the Site, or your intellectual property rights have been otherwise violated, please notify us for notice of claims of copyright or other intellectual property infringement by using the contact form listed on this site. 

Please provide the following in your Notice: 

a) Identify the material on the Site that you claim is infringing, with enough detail so that we may locate it on the Site; 

b) A statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; 

c) A statement by you declaring under penalty of perjury that (1) the above information in your notice is accurate, and (2) that you are the owner of the copyright interest involved or that you are authorized to act on behalf of that owner; 

d) Any other information as may be required by the DMCA and applicable law. 

Privacy Policy for selectarticle.net

The privacy of our visitors to selectarticle.net is important to us. 

At selectarticle.net, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit selectarticle.net, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

Log Files 

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

Cookies and Web Beacons 

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 

We also use third party advertisements on selectarticle.net to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

DoubleClick DART cookies 

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google's DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). 

The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. 

You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx 

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.
